Finding aid for the Machado and Silvetti Getty Villa renovation design records, 1994-2004 IA10019
Institutional Records and Archives
- Models, 1995-2000; Series II.
  - Entry court, circa late 1990s; (28 x 21 x 11) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 28)
  - Skylight gallery, circa late 1990s; (29 x 18 x 15) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 29)
  - [Small building, stairs and path], circa late 1990s; (16 x 11 x 14) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 30)
  - Exhibit pedestal, circa late 1990s; (19 x 9 x 11) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 31)
  - Garage, circa late 1990s; (24 x 17 x 8) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 32)
  - Entry Court, scheme B, February 1996; (29 x 19 x 14) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 33)
  - Site model, circa late 1990s; (33 x 22 x 7) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 34)
  - Site model with amphitheater, circa late 1990s; (70 x 34 5/8 x 23) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 35)
  - Site model without amphitheater, circa late 1990s; (37 1/2 x 25 1/2 x 16 1/4) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 36)
  - Site model, September 9, 1990; (118.2 x 57.5 x 31.5, 3/32"=1'0") (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 37 pt 2)
    Scope and Contents
    (Total height, with base, is 51". The model is in 3 sections, as is the base. This gives one the opportunity to understand sectional relationships between project elements and affords different viewpoints of the elements and context. This is the latest site model, but it does not represent the final plan. Shown Not included on this model are: the entire North Campus complex, the Central Plant, the South Parking structure, the Museum's north stair appendage, ancillary sitework, including batch lane improvements. In the model although no longer part of the proposal are improvements to existing art conservation structures around the Monkey Court (structures since demolished) and a loading dock appendage off of the east side of the Museum.
  - Model for contingency plan, circa late 1990s; (49 x 36 x 23) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 38)
  - Untitled, circa 1995-2000; (32 x 31 x 25) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 39)
  - North Campus Getty window detail, circa 1995-2000; (18 x 12 x 3.5) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 40)
  - Untitled, circa 1995-2000; (27 x 14.5 x 14) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 41)
  - Cafe detail, circa 1995-2000; (12 x 10 x 10) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 42)
  - Untitled, circa 1995-2000; (22.5 x 15 x 9) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 43)
  - Untitled, circa 1995-2000; (32 x 9 x 10) (Model 2004.IA.06 -model 44)
  - Site model with ocean, (15" x 26" x 48") (Box 2004.IA.05-Model 2)
  - Concept A, (Stored with 2004.IA.05-Model 5. Crate: 16" x 34" x 37") (Model 2004.IA.05 Models 4-5 Shared Crate)
  - Concept B, (Stored with 2004.IA.05-Model 4. Crate: 16" x 34" x 37") (Model 2004.IA.05 Models 4-5 Shared Crate)
- Project planning and administration, 1993-2001; Series III.; 45.2 Linear Feet (27 boxes, 6 flat files)
  The project planning and administration records of the Getty Villa and Ranch House renovation project primarily reflect the files of Machado and Silvetti associates Peter Lofgren (Associate in charge of the Masterplan Team, 1993-1996, Contracts and Entitlements Manager, 1996-unknown) and Tim Love (Associate in charge of the Masterplan Team, 1993-1996, Project Manager and Senior Designer, 1996-2002) dating from 1993-2001. They consist of administrative files, blueline prints, blueprints, black-and-white prints, and drawings.
  These records serve as an overview and summary of the project phases and include materials relating to associate architect and consultant selection, the space program and master plan, entitlements, budget and administrative issues. Also included are reference logs and subject files that provide a more detailed look at certain portions of the project including the Ranch House and conservation lab.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged into two sub-series:
  Series III.A. Peter Lofgren files, 1993-1998
  Series III.B. Tim Love files, 1993-2001.
  Series III.C. Planning photographs, undated.
  - Peter Lofgren files, 1993-1998; Series III.A.; 41.1 Linear Feet (24 boxes, 6 flat files)
    These records comprise of Machado and Silvetti associate Peter Lofgren's (Associate in charge of the Masterplan Team, 1993-1996, Contracts and Entitlements Manager, 1996-unknown) files relating to the renovation of the Getty Villa dating from 1993-1998. They consist of administrative files, blueline prints, blueprints, black-and-white prints, and drawings.
    These records serve as an overview and summary of the project phases and include materials relating to associate architect and consultant selection, the space program and master plan, entitlements, budget and administrative issues. Also included are reference logs and subject files that provide a more detailed look at certain portions of the project.
    - Contracts and agreements, 1994-1996
      Contains materials relating to contract negotiation between Machado and Silvetti and the J. Paul Getty Trust.
      The material is arranged chronologically.
      - CA architect registration, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Contracts / proposals, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Legal, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Contract, March 13, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Contracts / proposals, May 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Standard form of agreement between owner and architect, September 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Contracts: "Getty 141 and article 12 reference,", September 14, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Contract, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-115)
    - Villa Program: Space Program plans and Program Committee materials, 1993-1996
      Contains materials relating to the master and space program planning. This includes program summaries, project schedules and Villa Program Committee meeting notes and agendas.
      - Villa program summary, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        [The summary covers the following topics: space list and plans, collections, exhibitions, cast collection, multimedia presentations, artist-in-residence, performances, symposia, conservation / analytic, conservation processes, conservation training, and center for conservation education.]
      - Villa program summary, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Program information, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Program information, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-117)
        [Oversized material]
      - Binder: program and public relations, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - "From Villa program,", August 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-116)
      - Program summary and Langdon and Wilson architecture planning interiors, September 7, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-114)
      - Program summary, October 10, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Space Program, October 25, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-119)
        [Includes staff, office and support requirements.]
      - Project schedule, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Project schedule, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-117)
      - Master plan, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Master plan: background papers for board of trustees meeting, September 7-8, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-117)
      - Program: space estimate and square footage, March 13, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Villa program committee: memos and notes, April 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Phase I and II Space Program, June 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Loose material: Villa programming and calendar, October 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Project schedule, November 1, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Program, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Loose material: Villa program committee meeting agendas, December 1995-January 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
      - Villa Program Committee meetings, January 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Space Program, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Space Program, February 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-114)
      - Phase I Space Program, February 12, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-115)
      - Phase I Space Program, February 12, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-117)
      - Agendas and notes, Phase I Space Program, March 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Agendas and notes, Phase I Space Program, April 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Program, April 15, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Finish schedule, April 15, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
    - Associate architects, 1994
      Contains materials relating to the selection of an associate architect for the project. This includes proposals and brochures from the candidates and materials and correspondence from Langdon and Wilson, the firm chosen for the project.
      - Associate architect proposals / brochures, 1994; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Associate architect: Langdon and Wilson proposal, May 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Associate architect: compiled copy of proposals / brochures, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
        [Materials from Dworsky, Gensler, Gruen, Langdon and Wilson, and A. Martin.]
      - Associate architect: architect review notes, June 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
        Conditions Governing Access
        RESTRICTED. Materials (evaluation and interview materials) are permanently closed.
      - Associate architect: confidential, June 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Associate architect: interviews, June 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Associate architect notes, undated (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Associate architect: Langdon and Wilson, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Associate architect: Langdon and Wilson, July 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
      - Associate architect: Langdon and Wilson correspondence, June-July 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
    - Consultants, 1994-1996
      Contains brochures and proposals solicited during the consultant selection process and files relating to work with the consultants chosen for the project.
      The material is divided into two sections. Each section is arranged alphabetically.
      - Consultant proposals and selection, 1994-1995
        - Consultant proposals, 1994; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
          [Materials related to structural, mechanical, electrical, civil, geo-technical, landscape, traffic, cost estimating, EIR planning, graphics, acoustics and audio visual, lighting, food services, code, elevator and parking consultants.]
        - Consultant selection, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
        - Consultant materials: acoustics, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
        - Consultants: aerial photographers, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
        - Consultant materials: climate control, undated (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
        - Consultant materials: computer, CAD, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
        - Consultant materials: construction management, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-107)
        - Consultant materials: electrical, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Consultant materials: food service, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Consultant materials: mechanical engineers, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Consultant materials: Ove Arup and Partners, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Consultant materials: Ove Arup and Partners, August 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Consultant materials: security and seismic, undated (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Consultant materials: structural engineer, undated (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Consultant materials: structural engineer, undated (Box 2004.IA.06-114)
        - Photography: photogrammetry and maps, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-116)
      - Work with consultants, 1994-1996
        - Accessibility, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Code ADA, 1994-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Code: disabled access, May 30, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - "Consultant req's for CDS,", March 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Landscape, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Landscape, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Life safety correspondence and notes, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Lighting and millwork interiors scope, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Lighting design estimates and other correspondence, March-April 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Lighting, May-July 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Lighting, August-September 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-115)
        - Mechanical, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
        - Mechanical systems, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-108)
    - Entitlements, conditional use permits, environmental reviews, 1994-1996
      Contains materials relating to entitlements, conditional use permits (CUP) and environmental reviews. This includes correspondence, agendas, notes, drawings, and plans.
      For additional materials regarding entitlements, see flatfile 139.
      - Entitlements: Getty, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-115)
      - Entitlements: EIR, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements: Getty EIR, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements: EIR tasks, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements: miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements: PCR, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements summary, October 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements law, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements: drawings, January 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-109)
      - Entitlements, June 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-115)
    - Reference logs, 1996-1998
      Formerly housed in binders, these reference logs each contain materials about specific aspects of the Getty Villa renovation project, including correspondence, meeting minutes and notes, schedules, drawings and plans.
      The material within each reference log has been kept in its original order with the exception of oversized material. The reference logs have been arranged chronologically.
      For oversized materials found with the reference logs, see flatfiles 135, 136 and 138.
      - Loose floppy disk, undated (Box 2004.IA.06-110)
      - Reference log: sketch log, Ranch House, 1996-1997; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-117)
      - Reference log: museum basement 2, receiving, registrar, photo services, central plant, 1996-1997; (3 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-128)
      - Reference log: museum basement 3, preparations, packing / crating, mountmaking, 1996-1997; (3 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-129)
      - Reference log: museum basement 4, office services and engineering, 1996-1997; (4 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-121)
      - Reference log: general, events, security, grounds, 1996-1998; (3 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-125)
      - Reference log: conservation, 1996-1998; (4 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-130)
      - Reference log: Ranch House, Getty Research Institute, 1996-1999; (folder 1 of 5) (Box 2004.IA.06-125)
      - Reference log: Ranch House, Getty Research Institute, 1996-1999; (folders 2/5, 3/5, 4/5, 5/5) (Box 2004.IA.06-126)
      - Reference log: meeting minutes, Machado and Silvetti, 1996-1997 (Box 2004.IA.06-110)
      - Reference log: meeting minutes [material from middle of binder], 1997; (4 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-123)
      - Reference log: meeting minutes [material from binder front pocket], 1997; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-124)
      - Reference log: meeting minutes [material from binder back pocket], 1997 (Box 2004.IA.06-124)
      - Reference log: FF and E, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.06-110)
      - Reference log: FF and E, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.06-117)
      - Reference log: consultants, 1997; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-110)
      - Reference log: consultants, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.06-117)
      - Reference log: general, 1997; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-110)
        Contains materials related to scope, "SVC / FVC," scheduling, and budget.
      - Reference log: museum basement, education, slide library, exhibition design, antiquities storage, 1997; (3 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-120)
      - Reference log: millwork, 1997; (3 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-121)
      - Reference log: Ranch House lighting, 1997-1998; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-110)
      - Reference log: conservation, Getty Conservation Institute, monkey court, 1997-1998; (3 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-127)
    - Administrative files, 1993-1996
      Contains materials related to the administrative functions of Machado and Silvetti regarding the Getty Villa project. This includes meeting materials, chronological files, correspondence, drawing lists, directories and general materials.
      The material is divided into categories based on document type. Each category is arranged chronologically.
      - Meeting agendas, minutes and notes, 1994-1996
        - Meeting schedule and notes, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Binder: materials for meetings, July 20-22, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Binder: materials for meetings, July 20-22, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Meeting agenda, October-November 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Agenda, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Minutes and notes, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Structural meeting, November 2, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Agendas and notes: "Villa, December 12, 1995,", November 1995-January 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Loose agenda and project cost material, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Villa architect and meeting schedules, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Meeting minutes, December 1995-March 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Meeting minutes, April-August 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Notes, schedules, agendas and minutes, June-August 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - "Getty," notes, memos and meeting minutes, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
      - Chronological files, 1994-1995
        - Chronological file: "Getty Villa file,", October 1994-February 1995; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Chronological file, April 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-118)
        - Chronological file, May 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-118)
        - Chronological file, June 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-118)
        - Chronological file, July 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-118)
        - Chronological file, September-October 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-118)
      - Correspondence, 1993-1996
        - Correspondence, July 1993-May 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
        - Loose materials: notes, correspondence and organization chart, 1994-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
          [See box 115 for oversized materials related to the contents of this folder.]
        - Loose materials: correspondence, notes, task lists, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-111)
      - Drawing lists, 1994-1996
        - Sketchbook: Getty list of drawings, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        - Drawing lists: site information, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-116)
        - Drawings: "data base,", 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        - Drawing list, January 16, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        - Drawing list, January 16, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Directories, 1995-1996
        - Directory, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        - Directory, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - General administrative files, 1995-1996
        - Insurance, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        - Loose materials: schedules, schematic drawings and fee projections, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-115)
          [See box 111 for other materials related to the contents of this folder.]
        - Staff, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        - Letters of transmittal and shipping confirmations, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        - Project tasks, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        - Loose materials: staff and fee projections, July 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-116)
        - Loose materials: calendars and lighting memo, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        - Trustee presentation, September 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
    - Budget and cost estimates, 1994-1996
      Contains financial materials including invoices, cost estimates and budgets.
      - Invoices, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Estimate, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Program [cost estimates], 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Construction: conceptual budget estimate, July 18, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
        [Contains summary materials and materials related to the ranch house, conservation laboratory, museum basement, museum first floor, museum second floor, cafe and auditorium, amphitheater, entry pavilion and sitework.]
      - Langdon and Wilson: budget modifications, October 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Cost estimating, 1995-1996; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Cost estimating, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-115)
      - Cost estimate and program summary, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Loose materials: construction budget and schedule, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Master plan and schematic design estimates, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Loose materials: budget, design review, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
      - Loose materials: budget, design review, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-114)
      - Conceptual budget: display case and pedestal, April-May 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-112)
    - Subject Files, 1994-1996
      Contains materials related to detailed pieces of the project including exhibit design, food service, parking and traffic, and press and public relations. It also includes research materials about the Getty used by Machado and Silvetti during the development of the project.
      The material is divided into three categories (general, press releases and public relations and research files). Materials are arranged chronologically within each category.
      - General, 1994-1996
        - Drawings: photocopies of sections and elevations, undated (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Materials related to sketchbook: loose pages, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Sketchbook: loose pages, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-117)
        - Photographs, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Traffic correspondence and notes, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - "AAS models,", August 16, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Area calculations, November 30, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Untitled laboratory notebook, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Auditorium: classic theater, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Cafe: food service, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Getty Center (Brentwood), 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Loose materials: ceiling and photo studio notes, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Exhibit design: "preparations,", January 4, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Exhibit design: memo, January 8, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Getty conservation institute, January 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Mezzanine storage, February 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-115)
        - Parking, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-114)
        - Antiquities conservation, January 1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-114)
        - Antiquities curatorial, circa 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-114)
        - Model sample parts, undated (Box 2004.IA.06-116)
          [Examples of wood types for models. Taped to a piece of cardboard.]
        - Ranch House, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-114)
      - Press Releases and Public Relations, 1994-1996
        - Getty press clippings, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Public relations: Getty Villa renovation, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Press releases: Getty Villa renovation, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Getty Center articles, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
      - Research files, 1994
        - Research file: bibliography, [Getty], 1994 (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
        - Research file on the Getty Museum, programs and visitors, 1994; (5 folders) (Box 2004.IA.06-113)
    - Drawings, 1994-2000
      Contains sketches; notes; and blueline, blueprint and black-and-white bid sets, civil surveys, schematic designs, elevations, site plans, and lighting layouts.
      The material is arranged into two categories based on the size and type of the materials. The materials are arranged chronologically within the categories.
      - Bid sets, comments and corrections, 1998-2000
        - Ranch House comments, September 1998; (set of blueline prints, 15 x 21 inches) (Box 2004.IA.06-131)